^ ^ ^
( collective chatter )
WHAT AM I WORKING ON ?
UH , I 'M WORKING ON SOMETHING THAT 'LL CHANGE THE WORLD ,
AND HUMAN LIFE , AS WE KNOW IT .
CHANGE IT A LOT OR JUST A BIT ?
YOU 'LL HAVE TO BE MORE SPECIFIC .
DO YOU WANT ME TO BE SPECIFIC , HERE IN THIS ROOM ,
WITH , UH , HALF THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY
OF NORTH AMERICA EAVES DROPPING ?
IS THERE ANOTHER WAY ?
UH , YOU COULD COME BACK TO MY LAB .
LISTEN , I 'LL MAKE YOU A CAPPUCCINO .
I HAVE A FIAME OF MY VERY OWN .
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT IS ?
IT 'S NOT THE DILETTANTES PLASTIC KITCHEN MODEL .
IT 'S ONE OF THOSE , UH ,
REAL RESTAURANT ESPRESSO MACHINES ,
WITH THE EAGLE ON TOP .
SOMEHOW , I GET THE FEELING , YOU DON 'T GET OUT MUCH .
YOU CAN TELL THAT ?
YEAH .
I THINK YOU 'RE MAKING A MISTAKE .
I THINK YOU REALLY WANNA TALK TO ME .
SORRY- - I HAVE THREE OTHER INTERVIEWS TO DO ,
BEFORE THIS PARTY 'S OVER .
YEAH , BUT , THEY 'RE NOT WORKING ON SOMETHING ,
THAT 'LL CHANGE THE WORLD , AS WE KNOW IT .
THEY SAY , THEY ARE .
YEAH , BUT THEY 'RE LYING .
I 'M NOT .
( deeply inhaling )
ARE YOU SICK ?
( chuckling ) OH ... SURE .
YOU 'RE NOT A VERY ACCOMPLISHED DRUNK .
NO-NO , I 'M ALWAYS LIKE THIS .
IT 'S , UH , MOTION SICKNESS .
WHEN I WAS A KID , I , UH , PUKED ON MY TRICYCLE .
I HATE VEHICLES .
SHOULD I DRIVE MORE SLOWLY ?
NO-NO-NO , JUST TURN LEFT- - WE 'RE ALMOST THERE .
THIS IS IT ?
IT 'S , UH , CLEANER ON THE INSIDE .
PLEASE .
( playing piano )
LISTEN , UH , MAYBE , THIS IS A BAD IDEA .
OH , IT 'S TOO LATE .
YOU 'VE ALREADY SEEN THEM .
CAN 'T LET YOU LEAVE HERE ALIVE .
( playing eerie music on piano )
I HAVEN 'T SEEN ANYTHING .
THOSE .
DESIGNER PHONE BOOTHS- - VERY CUTE .
HEY , I BET YOU HAVE A REALLY NEAT JUKE BOX
IN HERE , TOO , SOMEPLACE .
OVER THERE , MAYBE ?
NO .
NO , THIS IS THE ... PROTOTYPE OF THOSE .
IT 'S THE FIRST ONE I HAD MADE .
IT , UH , WORKS , BUT , IT 'S CLUNKY .
( machines starting up )
I CALL THEM TELE-PODS .
THEY ARE CONTROLLED BY THIS .
THANK GOD , FOR THAT .
SO , UH , WHAT DO THEY DO , THE PHONE BOOTHS ?
TELE-PODS .
OH , UH , OKAY .
I NEED AN OBJECT , UM ...
SAY , DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING ON YOU
THAT 'S , UH , PERSONAL , THAT I COULD USE ?
SOMETHING UNIQUELY YOU ?
UH , AN ITEM OF CLOTHING OR JEWELRY ?
WHAT- - ARE YOU KIDDING ?
NO , I 'M SERIOUS .
OKAY- - HERE IT GOES .
UH-HUM .
I DON 'T WEAR JEWELRY .
IT 'S NICE .
UH , BRUNDLE , SETH .
( computerized voice ) UH , BRUNDLE , SETH .
( whispering )
UM , KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE STOCKING .
( machine buzzing louder )
WELL ?
GREAT .
THE WORLDS LARGEST MICROWAVE OVEN .
I 'M GLAD , I DIDN 'T GIVE YOU MY ROLEX ,
IF I HAD A ROLEX .
NO , YOU 'RE MISSING THE POINT .
LOOK .
TELEPORTATION ?
PLEASE .
( machine door opening )
OH , WAIT A MINUTE- - IS THAT A HOLOGRAM ?
WHERE 'S MY STOCKING ?
THAT 'S IT- - THE REAL ONE .
GO AHEAD- - PICK IT UP .
I DON 'T THINK I GET IT .
WHAT HAPPENED ?
YOU GET IT , ALL RIGHT- - YOU JUST CAN 'T HANDLE IT .
UM , YOUR STOCKING HAS JUST BEEN TELEPORTED
FROM ONE POD TO ANOTHER .
DISINTEGRATED THERE AND REINTEGRATED THERE ...
SORT OF .
IT WILL CHANGE THE WORLD , AS WE KNOW IT , RIGHT ?
OH , NO ...
( whispering ) HOT !
THIS IS- - THIS IS INCREDIBLE !
I MEAN , IT 'S NOT POSSIBLE , IS IT ?
HOW 'D YOU MANAGE TO KEEP THIS QUIET ?
PLEASE , SIT DOWN .
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS ALONE ?
WELL , I DON 'T WORK ALONE .
THERE 'S A LOT OF STUFF IN THERE ,
I DON 'T EVEN UNDERSTAND .
I 'M REALLY A-A SYSTEM 'S MANAGEMENT MAN .
I FARM BITS AND PIECES , UH ,
OUT TO GUYS WHO ARE MUCH MORE BRILLIANT , THAN I AM .
I SAY " BUILD ME A LASER OF THIS ,
" DESIGN ME A MOLECULAR ANALYZER OF THAT , "
AND THEY DO AND I JUST STICK ' EM TOGETHER .
BUT , UH , NONE OF THEM
KNOWS WHAT THE PROJECT REALLY IS , SO ...
WOW !
AND , UH , THE MONEY ?
BARTECH SCIENCE INDUSTRIES FINANCED THIS ?
UH-HUM , BUT , THEY LEAVE ME ALONE ,
'CAUSE I 'M NOT EXPENSIVE .
AND , UH , THEY KNOW , THEY 'LL END UP OWNING IT ALL ,
WHATEVER IT IS , SO ...
( Veronica ) YOU HAVEN 'T TOLD THEM ?
WHEN I 'M READY .
( beeping ) OH , WAIT A SECOND !
WHAT 'S THAT ?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
WELL , YOU WANT ME TO GET THE QUOTES RIGHT ,
DON 'T YOU ?
QUOTES ?
NO-NO-NO , I THOUGHT THIS WAS PERSONAL .
YOU CAN 'T WRITE ABOUT THIS .
WHAT ARE YOU TALKG ABOU
I 'M A JOURNALIST .
OH , NO-NO-NO-NO-NO !
YOU KNEW THAT .
UH , I 'M SORRY- - I APOLOGIZE .
I MADE A MISTAKE .
I SHOULDN 'T HAVE SHOWN YOU THIS .
I 'M VERY , VERY SORRY .
LISTEN , " PARTICLE MAGAZINE "
SENT ME TO THAT PARTY TO GET A STORY ,
AND THIS IS THE MOST EXCITING THING , I 'VE EVER SEEN .
NO , NO- - ABSOLUTELY NOT !
IN FACT , I 'M GOING TO HAVE TO ASK YOU FOR THAT TAPE , PLEASE ?
YOU CAN 'T DO THAT .
DON 'T YOU DARE WRITE A STORY !
I 'D NEVER 'VE TOLD ANY OF THIS STUFF TO A JOURNALIST .
BUT , YOU DID TELL THIS STUFF TO A JOURNALIST .
WELL , YEAH , IN A WAY , I SUPPOSE I DID , BUT- - SURE DID .
NOW , WAIT A MINUTE- - WAIT A MINUTE .
WAIT- - COME HERE !
WHAT ABOUT YOUR STOCKING ?
KEEP IT FOR GOOD LUCK .
( Veronica on tape recorder ) THE MONEY- - BARTECH SCIENCE INDUSTRIES FINANCED THIS ?
( Seth on tape recorder ) UH-HUH , BUT , THEY LEAVE ME ALONE ,
'CAUSE I 'M NOT EXPENSIVE .
AND , UH , THEY KNOW , THEY 'LL END UP OWNING IT ALL ,
WHATEVER IT IS , SO ...
( tape shuts off )
WELL , THAT 'S IT .
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
IT 'S A JOKE .
WHAT ?
HE 'S CONNING YOU .
OH , IT 'S AN OLD NIGHT CLUB ROUTINE .
THE TWO CABINETS ,
AND YOU FELL FOR IT .
( telephone ringing ) WAIT A MINUTE- - THAT WAS NO NIGHT CLUB .
ARE WE HAVING LUNCH ?
LISTEN , THAT WAS NO NIGHT CLUB ROUTINE !
I WAS THERE- - I SAW IT !
YEAH ?
SURE , SEND HIM IN .
YOU MUST 'VE MADE AN IMPRESSION .
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
YOUR MAGICIAN HAS FOLLOWED YOU HERE .
( knocking on door )
I 'M STATHIS BORANS .
I 'M THE EDITOR OF " PARTICLE MAGAZINE . "
UH , SETH BRUNDLE .
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE .
UH , LISTEN- - WHY DON 'T YOU TWO USE MY OFFICE .
I 'VE GOTTA RUN .
IF YOU PLAN TO MAKE ANYTHING DISAPPEAR ,
PLEASE , LET ME KNOW .
I 'VE GOT AN ASSISTANT EDITOR
WHO 'S OUTLIVED HIS USEFULNESS .
YOU DIDN 'T WASTE ANY TIME .
I 'M NOT GETTING ANY YOUNGER .
HE DIDN 'T SEEM- - HE WASN 'T IMPRESSED BY YOUR TAPE ?
HE THINKS YOU 'RE A CON MAN .
EXCELLENT !
YEAH , WELL , LET 'S SEE WHAT THE PEOPLE AT OMNI , THINK ABOUT IT .
NO , NO , LISTEN , VERONICA ...
I 'VE COME HERE TO SAY ONE MAGIC WORD TO YOU .
YEAH .
CHEESEBURGER .
( chuckling )
I 'VE BEEN WORKING ALONE , TOO LONG .
I HAVE A STRONG URGE , UH , TO TALK ABOUT WHAT I 'M DOING .
BUT , UM , IF THIS GETS OUT , NOW , VERONICA ,
IT 'LL KILL ME .
THE BARTECH PEOPLE WILL KILL ME ,
MY COLLEAGUES WILL KILL ME .
IT 'S NOT READY , YET .
SEEMS TO WORK OKAY .
NO , SOMETHING IMPORTANT 'S MISSING .
YEAH ?
YEAH .
WHICH IS ?
I CAN ONLY TELE-PORT INANIMATE OBJECTS .
WELL , WHAT HAPPENS , WHEN YOU TRY TO TELE-PORT LIVING THINGS ?
NOT WHILE WE 'RE EATING .
IT CAN 'T BE WORSE , THAN THIS !
LISTEN- - YOU 'RE NOT DOING A VERY GOOD JOB OF CONVINCING ME .
I THINK THE WORLD SHOULD KNOW ABOUT IT , NOW ,
AND I THINK I SHOULD BE THE ONE TO TELL IT .
YOU SHOULD TELL IT , BUT , UH , NOT YET .
LOOK , WHAT DO YOU GOT , SO FAR ?
ENOUGH TO MAKE YOU NERVOUS .
WHY NOT GET MORE ?
LET ME BECOME YOUR MAJOR PROJECT .
I 'M TALKING ABOUT A BOOK , NOT A MAGAZINE ARTICLE .
FOLLOW ME AND MY WORK , DAY BY DAY ,
IN AS MUCH DETAIL , AS YOU CAN STAND .
I DON 'T HAVE A LIFE ,
SO , THERE 'S NOTHING FOR YOU TO INTERFERE WITH .
RESEARCH THE BACKGROUND , COVER THE PROCESS .
A COMPLETE RECORD OF THE MOST
EARTH SHATTERING INVENTION EVER .
THE ONE THAT ENDED ALL CONCEPTS OF TRANSPORT ,
OF BORDERS AND FRONTIERS , OF TIME AND SPACE .
YOUR BOOK WILL END WITH ME ,
TRANSPORTING MYSELF 15-FEET THROUGH SPACE ,
FROM ONE TELE-POD TO ANOTHER .
THAT 'S WHAT 'S REALLY MISSING .
WAIT FOR ME THAT LONG ?
( shower water ruing )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN MY APARTMENT ?
I JUST HAPPENED TO BE IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD .
FELT A BIT SCUMMY .
ROUGH DAY .
( toilet flushing )
AH-AH-OW !
HOW DID YOU GET IN ?
I HAVE A KEY , REMEMBER ?
YOU GAVE IT TO ME .
I KNOW I SHOULD 'VE CHANGED THE LOCK .
I KNEW , YOU WOULDN 'T .
YEAH ? YEAH .
THAT 'S BECAUSE , UNCONSCIOUSLY ...
YOU STILL WANT ME TO COME BACK ,
MOVE IN , AGAIN .
NO .
THAT 'S BECAUSE , VERY CONSCIOUSLY ,
I 'M LAZY AND DISORGANIZED .
YOUR NEW PLAYMATE 'S AN INTERESTING GUY .
WHAT PLAYMATE ?
THE NIGHT CLUB ACT ...
BRUNDLE .
YEAH ?
YEAH .
YOU KNOW , I WAS WRONG .
HE 'S REALLY QUITE BRILLIANT .
HE WAS THE LEADER OF THE F-THREE-TWO TEAM .
REMEMBER THEM ?
AN INCH AWAY FROM THE NOBLE PRIZE FOR PHYSICS .
HE WAS ONLY 20 , AT THE TIME .
UM , I DON 'T EVEN THINK I 'M GONNA DO BRUNDLE .
I 'M STILL CONSIDERING THE " PSYCHOLOGY TODAY " GIG .
THAT 'S NOT LIKE YOU .
ARE YOU GETTING OUT , OR AM I ?
I 'LL GO .
I HAVE TO PUT THIS ISSUE TO BED .
YOU WANT ME TO COME BACK LATER AND TUCK YOU IN ?
NO .
KEY !
I 'LL KEEP IT ...
FOR OLD TIME SAKE .
YOU 'RE A PETTY SCHMUCK .
( chuckling )
INITIATING FIVE SECONDS .
( machine running )
^ ^ ^
( loud bang )
( bubbling and squelching )
( Veronica ) YOU 'VE GOTTA DO THIS , SETH .
TALK TO THE TAPE- - GET IN THE HABIT .
THE WORLD WILL WANNA KNOW WHAT YOU 'RE THINKING .
WHY DIDN 'T IT WORK ?
I THINK , UH , IT TURNED THE BABOON INSIDE OUT .
WHY ?
CAN 'T DEAL WITH THE FLESH .
IT ONLY SEEMS TO WORK WITH INANIMATE OBJECTS .
NOTHING THAT 'S LIVING .
IT MUST BE MY FAULT .
( Veronica ) WHY ?
COMPUTERS ARE DUMB .
THEY ONLY KNOW , WHAT YOU TELL THEM .
I MUST NOT KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT THE FLESH , MYSELF .
I 'M GONNA HAVE TO LEARN .
I DON 'T WANNA TALK , NOW .
^ ^ ^
DO YOU EVER CHANGE YOUR CLOTHES ?
WHAT ?
YOUR CLOTHES ...
YOU 'RE ALWAYS WEARING THE SAME CLOTHES .
NO , THESE ARE CLEAN .
I CHANGE MY CLOTHES , EVERY DAY .
FIVE SETS OF EXACTLY THE SAME CLOTHES ?
I LEARNED IT FROM EINSTEIN .
THIS WAY , I DON 'T HAVE TO , UM ,
EXPEND ANY THOUGHT ON WHAT I 'M GONNA WEAR .
I JUST GRAB THE NEXT SET ON THE RACK .
I BOUGHT SOME STEAKS .
CAN I MAKE YOU ONE ?
WE COULD GO OUT .
CHEESEBURGER ?
NO , UH , WE DON 'T HAVE TO GO THERE .
YOU 'RE VERY CUTE , YOU KNOW THAT ?
AM I ?
^ ^ ^
( breathing heavily )
OH , OW !
MY BACK , OW !
OH !
OH , GOD , SOMETHING 'S STUCK TO YOUR BACK ?
WELL , HELP PULL IT OFF .
UH !
OH-OH !
OW !
SORRY .
OH , I WONDERED WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT .
DO YOU HAVE ANY DISINFECTANT ?
UH , IT 'S OKAY .
I WANT TO KISS IT FOR YOU .
OH .
BABE ... HMM ?
THANK YOU .
( playful growling ) OW-OW !
SORRY- - I JUST WANT TO EAT YOU UP .
YOU KNOW , THAT 'S WHY OLD LADIES PINCH BABIES CHEEKS .
IT 'S THE FLESH- - IT JUST MAKES YOU CRAZY .
RIGHT-RIGHT . HMM .
YOU WANNA TRY AN EXPERIMENT ?
SURE .
^ ^ ^
( grease sizzling )
( sighing ) OKAY .
EAT THIS AND I NEED AN OBJECTIVE OPINION .
YES ?
WELL , IT COULD USE SOME FINESSE ,
BUT , UM , IT TASTES LIKE A STEAK .
OKAY ... NOW , TRY THIS TELEPORTED HALF .
OH , ARE YOU SERIOUS ?
A MONKEY JUST CAME APART IN THERE .
BABOON- - EAT .
OH , UM , THAT TASTES FUNNY .
FUNNY HOW ?
IT TASTE , UM ... SYNTHETIC .
MMM-HMM .
SO , WHAT HAVE WE PROVED ?
THE COMPUTER IS GIVING US IT 'S INTERPRETATION OF A STEAK .
IT 'S , UH , TRANSLATING IT FOR US .
IT 'S RE-THINKING IT , RATHER THAN REPRODUCING IT
AND SOMETHING IS GETTING LOST IN THE TRANSLATION .
ME .
I 'M LOST .
THE FLESH .
IT SHOULD MAKE THE COMPUTER , UH , CRAZY ,
LIKE THOSE OLD LADIES PINCHING BABIES .
BUT , IT DOESN 'T- - NOT YET .
I HAVEN 'T TAUGHT THE COMPUTER TO BE MADE CRAZY
BY THE , UH ...
FLESH , THE POETRY , THE STEAK .
SO , I 'M GONNA START TEACHING IT , NOW .
^ ^ ^
( car engine starting )
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN IT .
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
I FOLLOWED YOU .
" PSYCHOLOGY TODAY , " MY ASS !
YOU STAYED WITH BRUNDLE , ALL NIGHT .
WHY DIDN 'T I BELIEVE YOU ?
I WONDER ?
OH , YEAH-YEAH .
YEAH , I THINK YOU 'D LOOK GREAT IN THIS .
DON 'T YOU ?
HUH ?
I MEAN , FOR YOUR " TIME MAGAZINE " COVER ,
YOU 'VE GOTTA LOOK GOOD , RIGHT ?
DON 'T YOU GET IT ?
I AM FINALLY ON TO SOMETHING THAT 'S BIG .
TOO PERFECT TO BELIEVE .
YOU 'RE A GODDESS .
THANK YOU FOR MAKING MY MOST PARANOID FANTASY 'S COME TRUE .
I DON 'T HAVE TO REPORT TO YOU , YOU CREEP !
RONNI !
YOU 'VE GOT TO TALK TO ME !
I DON 'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING .
WE 'RE FINISHED , REMEMBER ?
I 'LL SPEND THE NIGHT , ANYWHERE , I DAMN WELL PLEASE !
SORRY , UH , I 'LL TAKE THIS , TOO .
^ ^ ^
( baboon screeching )
I THINK IT 'S TIME FOR CHAMPAGNE .
OH , GOD , SETH .
IT 'S REALLY HAPPENED .
YOU DID IT .
YOU 'LL NEVER HAVE TO GET CAR SICK , AGAIN .
OR AIR SICK OR SEA SICK .
OH , I KNOW-I KNOW , OR TRICYCLE SICK .
WHAT 'S NEXT ?
WELL , I 'LL SEND THE BABOON OUT FOR TESTS- -
SEE IF HE 'S REALLY OKAY .
HOW LONG WILL THAT TAKE ?
IT COULD BE WEEKS .
REALLY ?
YEAH , WHY ?
WELL , I WAS THINKING THAT WE COULD TAKE A HOLIDAY .
WE COULD ?
YEAH .
YOU KNOW , LIKE AN OLD MARRIED COUPLE .
THE OLD MAN 'S GOT A COUPLE WEEKS OFF ,
SO , THEY GO TO FLORIDA- - SOME PLACE WARM .
JUST YOU AND ME ?
YEAH , WHY ?
IS THERE SOMEONE ELSE
YOU WHERE THINKING OF BRINGING ALONG ?
NO-NO , I JUST ...
IS THIS A ROMANCE WE 'RE HAVING ?
IS THAT WHAT IT IS ?
YEAH , IT COULD BE A ROMANCE .
COME HERE .
I HAVE A GREAT IDEA .
YOU LIKE CHINESE FOOD ?
YES .
WE 'RE GOING TO HAVE A VERY ROMANTIC DINNER , RIGHT HERE .
HEY , WHAT 'S THIS ?
OH , YEAH , FROM YOUR EDITOR .
I 'M SORRY , SOMEBODY SLIPPED IT UNDER THE DOOR .
HELLO , VICTOR- - YEAH , IT 'S SETH BRUNDLE .
OH , Y-YEAH- - I 'LL WAIT .
( Veronica ) OH , NO !
( Seth ) WHAT ?
WHAT 'S THAT ?
UM ...
NOTHING- - IT 'S JUST , UH , PERSONAL ( deleted ) .
I THOUGHT OLD MARRIED COUPLES
SHARED ALL THEIR PERSONAL ( deleted ) .
THAT 'S HOW THEY STAYED OLD AND MARRIED .
UH , LISTEN , SETH- - DON 'T RUSH IT .
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
LOOK , I HAVE TO GO OUT FOR A FEW HOURS .
NOW ?
NO , RONNI- - SPICY EGG PLANT , CHAMPAGNE .
JUST FOR A FEW HOURS .
I STILL HAVE THE RESIDUE OF ANOTHER LIFE , YOU KNOW ?
I-I HAVE TO SCRAPE IT OFF MY SHOE
AND GET RID OF IT , ONCE AND FOR ALL .
^ ^ ^
( Veronica ) WHAT 'S THIS SUPPOSE TO MEAN ?
IT MEANS , THAT I 'M YOUR EDITOR
AND I 'M SHAPING YOUR MATERIAL INTO A STORY .
YOU 'RE THE ONE WHO TOLD ME , THERE WAS NO STORY .
YOU SAID , BRUNDLE WAS A CON MAN .
I 'VE DECIDED TO TRUST YOUR JOURNALISTIC INSTINCTS .
THANKS , VERY MUCH ,
BUT , THIS IS NOT YOUR STORY , IT 'S MINE .
SAYS WHO ?
I SENT YOU TO THE BARTECH PARTY
TO SEE WHAT YOU COULD FIND .
YOUR DISCOVERY IS MY DISCOVERY .
I HAVE A LOT OF BACKGROUND ON BRUNDLE .
HE 'S BEEN WORKING ON THIS THING FOR SIX YEARS .
THERE 'S MATERIAL OUT THERE TO FIND , IF YOU DIG DEEP .
I DUG .
STATHIS , EVERYTHING THAT HAS TO DO WITH TRANSPORTATION
WILL BECOME OBSOLETE ,
AND I AM RIGHT THERE IN THE MIDDLE OF IT !
THE ONLY RECORDER OF THE EVENT , FROM THE INSIDE OUT !
OKAY .
LOOK- - JUST KEEP ME INFORMED .
ALL RIGHT ?
AS A FRIEND .
AS A PROFESSIONAL CONFIDANTE .
THAT 'S ALL ?
I DON 'T WANT YOU TO DISAPPEAR FROM MY LIFE .
( sighing )
OKAY .
WHAT ABOUT SEX ?
UH , I 'M NOT SAYING LOVE OR AFFECTION- -
JUST STRESS RELIEVING SEX , YOU AND ME ?
YOU 'RE DISGUSTING , AS ALWAYS .
DON 'T WANNA DISAPPOINT YOU .
" RESIDUE " MEANS HER OLD BOYFRIEND , DOESN 'T IT ?
STATHIS BORANS IS HER OLD BOYFRIEND .
FROM THE DESK OF STATHIS BORANS .
HOW ABOUT UNDER THE DESK OF STATHIS BORANS ?
SHE 'S WORKING FOR HER OLD BOYFRIEND .
NOW , SHE RUNS OUT LATE AT NIGHT , TO SEE HIM .
WHAT IS THIS- - THE RONNIE GAME ?
( baboon gurgling )
I 'M CATCHING ON- - I 'M CATCHING ON .
I DIDN 'T MEAN TO KILL YOUR BROTHER ,
( fly buzzing ) BUT , HE DIDN 'T DIE IN VEIN , IF THAT 'S ANY COMFORT ?
AND , AS THE GENERAL SAID ,
" THERE 'S NOTHING I 'D ASK YOU TO DO ,
" THAT I WOULDN 'T DO , MYSELF , BOYS . "
( fly buzzing )
HEY , YOU 'RE ALL RIGHT .
I 'M LOOKING AT YA- - I CAN TELL , YOU 'RE OKAY .
WHAT ARE WE WAITIN ' FOR ?
LETS DO IT .
^ ^ ^
( fly buzzing )
( machine starting up )
^ ^ ^
HOW YOU DOING ?
HEY , YOU TELL ME .
AM I DIFFERENT , SOMEHOW ?
IS IT ALIVE OR IS IT MEMOREX ?
IT 'S TOO BAD RONNIE MISSED IT .
^ ^ ^
( eerie music playing )
I MISSED YOU , LAST NIGHT .
IT 'S STILL NIGHT- - I CAME BACK .
YOU HAD TO CELEBRATE WITHOUT ME .
I 'M SORRY .
I WENT THROUGH , LAST NIGHT .
YOU WENT THROUGH ?
WITHOUT TESTING THE BABOON ?
I WAS DRUNK- - I WAS A BIT UPSET .
YOU COULD HAVE KILLED YOURSELF .
ARE YOU SLEEPING WITH STATHIS BORANS ?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
I-I JUST , UH , GET THAT FEELING .
THAT 'S WHY YOU WHERE UPSET ?
I GOT JEALOUS .
OH , GOD , SETH !
YOU DON 'T HAVE TO BE JEALOUS .
HE 'S AN OLD BOYFRIEND .
HE WAS TEACHING AT COLLEGE .
I WAS A SCIENCE MAJOR .
HE GOT ME STARTED IN JOURNALISM .
IS HE STILL IN LOVE WITH YOU ?
HOW COULD HE NOT BE ?
HEY , WHAT ABOUT OUR DEAL ?
YOU WENT THROUGH AND I WASN 'T THERE .
DON 'T WORRY- - I TAPED IT FOR YOU .
YOU DID ?
YEAH .
^ ^ ^
( fly buzzing )
( buzzing stops )
^ ^ ^
( breathing hard )
( feet pounding ceiling )
( feet hitting ceiling again )
^ ^ ^
( collective talking )
( Seth ) SO , I ASKED THE COMPUTER , IF IT HAD IMPROVED ME .
IT SAID , " IT DIDN 'T KNOW WHAT I WAS TALKING ABOUT , "
AND THAT 'S MADE ME THINK , VERY CAREFULLY ,
ABOUT WHAT I 'VE BEEN FEELING AND WHY .
I 'M BEGINNING TO THINK
THAT THE SHEER PROCESS OF BEING TAKEN APART , OUT OF BODY ,
AND PUT BACK TOGETHER , AGAIN ...
WHY , IT 'S LIKE COFFEE BEING PUT THROUGH A FILTER .
IT 'S SOMEHOW , A PURIFYING PROCESS .
IT 'S PURIFIED ME , IT 'S CLEANSED ME ,
AND I 'LL TELL YA ,
I THINK IT 'S GOING TO ALLOW ME TO REALIZE ...
THE PERSONAL POTENTIAL I 'VE BEEN NEGLECTING ,
ALL THESE YEARS-- -
THAT I 'VE BEEN OBSESSIVELY PURSUING , GOAL AFTER GOAL .
DO YOU NORMALLY TAKE COFFEE WITH YOUR SUGAR ?
WHAT ?
YOU KNOW , I-I JUST DON 'T THINK
I 'VE EVER GIVEN ME A CHANCE TO BE ME .
BUT , OF COURSE , INTERESTINGLY ,
AT THE EXACT SAME MOMENT THAT I ACHIEVE ,
WHAT 'LL PROBABLY PROVE TO BE MY LIFE 'S WORK ,
THAT 'S THE MOMENT ,
WHEN I START BEING THE REAL ME , FINALLY .
SO , UH , LISTEN , NOT TO WAX MESSIAHONIC ,
BUT , UH , IT MAY BE TRUE ,
THAT THE SYNCHRONICITY OF THOSE TWO EVENTS
MIGHT BLUR THE REST AND INDIVIDUAL EFFECT
OF EITHER , INDIVIDUALLY .
BUT , IT IS , NEVERTHELESS , ALSO CERTAINLY TRUE ,
I WILL SAY , NOW , HOWEVER , SUBJECTIVELY ,
THAT HUMAN TELEPORTATION ,
MOLECULAR DECIMATION BREAK DOWN
AND REFORMATION IS INHERENTLY PURGING .
IT MAKES A MAN A KING .
FROM THE MOMENT I WALKED OUT OF THE POD ,
I FELT LIKE A MILLION BUCKS .
YOU KNOW , I THINK I AM GONNA HAVE ,
UH , CANNOLI , AFTER ALL .
WAITER !
I MEAN , WHAT AN ACCOMPLISHMENT .
BUT , WHAT HAVE I REALLY DONE ?
ALL I 'VE DONE , IS SAY TO THE WORLD ,
" LET 'S GO- - MOVE !
" CATCH ME IF YOU CAN ! "
WAITER- - JESUS !
^ ^ ^
OH , HOW CAN YOU KEEP GOING ?
YOU CAN 'T HAVE ANY FLUID LEFT IN YOUR BODY .
WE 'VE BEEN DOING THIS FOR HOURS .
I 'M NOT READY TO QUIT , YET .
COME ON .
HEY , WHAT 'S THIS ?
IT 'S AN ATTEMPT TO DISTRACT ME- - THAT 'S WHAT IT IS .
NO , REALLY- - WHAT IS THIS ?
IT 'S , LIKE , HAIRS OR SOMETHING .
I DON 'T KNOW .
IT HAPPENS , WHEN YOU GET OLDER .
WEIRD HAIR CONFIGURATIONS , I DON 'T KNOW .
THEY 'RE REALLY COARSE .
WELL , I 'VE NEVER REALLY BEEN HAIRY ENOUGH .
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN ?
ALWAYS TOO ... BOYISH .
I 'M LOOKING FORWARD TO A HAIRY BODY .
IT 'S ONE OF THE COMPENSATIONS OF OLD AGE .
COME HERE- - WHERE YOU GOING ?
I 'M GONNA GET UP .
HEY-HEY-HEY- - NOT MY NEW HAIR .
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
RELAX , BRUNDLE .
I DON 'T REALLY THINK YOU WANT A BODY COVERED WITH THESE .
GOD , THEY 'RE REALLY TOUGH .
( slamming spoon down )
LISTEN ... I WANT YOU TO GO THROUGH .
I WANT TO TELE-PORT YOU ,
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE , RIGHT NOW .
YOU 'LL FEEL INCREDIBLE .
RONNIE , I HARDLY NEED TO SLEEP , ANYMORE ,
AND I FEEL WONDERFUL .
IT 'S LIKE A DRUG ,
BUT , A PERFECTLY PURE AND BENIGN DRUG .
THE POWER I FEEL SURGING INSIDE ME- -
AND I WON 'T BE ABLE TO WEAR YOU OUT .
WE 'LL BE THE PERFECT COUPLE .
THE DYNAMIC DUO .
COME ON- - RIGHT NOW .
NO , HEY- - WAIT !
DON 'T GIVE ME THAT BORN AGAIN TELEPORTATION WRAP .
I TOLD YOU , I WAS SCARED TO DO IT .
WHAT DO I HAVE TO SAY ?
I 'M NOT GONNA DO IT !
( shouting ) YOU 'RE A ( deleted ) DRAG , YOU KNOW THAT ?
SOMETHING WENT WRONG , SETH .
WHEN YOU WENT THROUGH , SOMETHING WENT WRONG .
NO , NOT YOU ?
YOU 'RE TOO CHICKEN ( deleted )
TO BE A MEMBER OF THE DYNAMIC DUO CLUB ?
OKAY , THEN , GREAT .
I 'LL FIND SOMEBODY ELSE .
SOMEBODY WHO CAN KEEP UP WITH ME .
SETH , YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME .
YOU 'RE AFRAID TO DIVE INTO THE PLASMA POOL , AREN 'T YOU ?
YOU 'RE AFRAID TO BE DESTROYED
AND RECREATED , AREN 'T YOU ?
I BET YOU THINK THAT YOU WOKE ME UP
ABOUT THE FLESH , DON 'T YOU ?
BUT , YOU ONLY KNOW SOCIETY 'S STRAIGHT LINE ABOUT THE FLESH .
YOU CAN 'T PENETRATE BEYOND
SOCIETY 'S SICK , GRAVE FEAR OF THE FLESH !
DRINK DEEP OR TASTE NOT THE PLASMA SPRING !
SEE WHAT I 'M SAYING ?
AND I 'M NOT JUST TALKING ABOUT SEX AND PENETRATION .
I 'M TALKING ABOUT PENETRATION ,
BEYOND THE VEIL OF THE FLESH .
A DEEP , PENETRATING DIVE INTO THE PLASMA POOL !
^ ^ ^
( music from juke box )
SCOTCH .
WHO 'S WINNING ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
I HOPE , IT 'S MARKY .
HOW COME ?
'CAUSE , I LIKE MARKY , TONIGHT .
WELL , I LIKE YOU , TONIGHT .
MAYBE , I 'D BETTER GET INVOLVED IN THIS , TOO .
HEY , PAL , YOU 'RE DISTURBING US .
I GOT A HUNDRED BUCKS
SAYS I CAN BEAT EITHER ONE OF YOU .
( laughing )
TAKE A HIKE , ASS ( deleted ) !
HERE ...
THERE 'S MY HUNDRED ,
AND I GET TO TAKE THE LADY HOME FOR THE NIGHT , IF I WIN .
SAYS WHO ?
DO I LOOK LIKE A HOOKER TO YOU ?
HEY , TAWNY , IT 'S AN EASY HUNDRED .
COME ON , PAL- - LETS GET IT OVER WITH .
YOU BETTER WATCH OUT- - HE EATS CHOCOLATE BARS .
( chuckling ) YEAH , SO , I NOTICED .
^ ^ ^
( screaming in pain )
( Tawny ) ARE YOU A BODY BUILDER OR SOMETHING ?
( Seth ) YEAH , I BUILD BODIES .
I TAKE ' EM APART AND THEN , I PUT EM BACK TOGETHER , AGAIN .
( Tawny ) WELL , YOU SURE TOOK MARKY APART .
( Seth ) LETS GO BACK TO MY PLACE .
( Tawny ) YOUR PLACE ?
YEAH , WELL , OKAY- - I LIVE WITH MY MOTHER , ANYWAY .
BUT , UH , CAN WE MAYBE , GO TO A FEW MORE BARS , FIRST ?
I MEAN , IT 'S A LITTLE TOO EARLY TO QUIT .
SURE , A FEW MORE BARS .
( birds chirping )
GREAT PLACE .
HEY !
THERE 'S NO ELEVATOR .
I CAN 'T MAKE IT .
NO , THERE 'S AN ELEVATOR .
NOW , DON 'T YOU FEEL ELEVATED ?
WHOA !
^ ^ ^
( Tawny ) WOW !
ARE YOU SOME SORT OF MAGICIAN ?
YES .
SO , ARE WE GOING TO BREAKST OR NOT ?
IT 'S YOUR TURN .
TO DO WHAT ?
I WANT YOU TO GO THROUGH .
NO , I DON 'T WANNA TRY THAT .
WHY NOT- - IT 'LL MAKE YOU FEEL SEXY .
BUT , I ALREADY FEEL SEXY .
HOW ABOUT A NICE ALCOHOL RUB ?
DON 'T DO THAT- - IT HURTS !
SORRY , HON .
I DIDN 'T KNOW YOU HAD THE SKIN OF A PRINCESS .
YOU 'RE REAL SENSITIVE , HUH ?
OKAY-OKAY , THAT 'S IT !
I DON 'T WANT TO- - I 'M AFRAID !
DON 'T BE AFRAID !
NO , BE AFRAID- - BE VERY AFRAID .
WHO 'S THIS ?
OH , I FORGOT TO TELL YOU .
I LIVE WITH MY MOTHER , TOO .
MOM , MEET TAWNY .
I GOTTA GO .
THANKS FOR A WONDERFUL TIME .
WHY 'D YOU SCARE HER OFF ?
JEALOUS ?
YOU 'RE CHANGING , SETH .
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU IS CHANGING .
YOU LOOK BAD ...
YOU SMELL BAD .
I 'VE NEVER BEEN MUCH OF A BATHER .
THOSE WEIRD HAIRS THAT WERE GROWING OUT OF YOUR BACK ,
I TOOK THEM TO A LAB .
I HAD THEM ANALYZED .
THE HAIRS ?
OH , YEAH , THAT 'S A STRANGE THING TO DO .
NOT AS STRANGE , AS THE RESULTS .
THE GUY AT THE LAB HAD TROUBLE IDENTIFYING THEM .
HE FINALLY CAME TO THE CONCLUSION ,
THAT THEY WERE DEFINITELY NOT HUMAN .
OH , VERY GOOD .
NOT HUMAN , SETH !
IN FACT , VERY LIKELY , INSECT HAIRS .
THAT 'S SILLY- - THAT 'S RIDICULOUS .
LOOK- - NOW , THERE 'S MORE !
LOOK AT YOUR FACE !
SOMETHING HAPPENED , WHEN YOU WENT THROUGH , SETH .
YOU 'VE GOT TO GET SOME HELP .
I THINK YOU MUST BE SICK .
( yelling ) YOU 'RE JEALOUS !
I 'VE BECOME FREE , I 'VE BEEN RELEASED
AND YOU CAN 'T STAND IT .
YOU 'LL DO ANYTHING TO BRING ME DOWN .
LOOK AT ME- - DOES THIS LOOK SICK ?
DOES THIS LOOK LIKE A SICK MAN TO YOU ?
NO !
STOP IT !
KNOW ANY SICK MAN , WHO CAN DO THAT ?
COME HERE .
NO , SETH- - DEALS OFF- - I DON 'T NEED YOU , ANYMORE .
NO , WAIT- - SETH , PLEASE !
WAIT !
SETH !
DON 'T COME BACK !
OH , GOD !
^ ^ ^
( crying )
( electric shaver buzzing )
OW !
( tearing sound )
earing sound )
^ ^ ^
( gasping )
OH , NO !
WHAT 'S HAPPENING TO ME ?
AM I DYING ?
IS THIS HOW IT STARTS , WHEN I DIE ?
( Seth ) BRUNDLE , SETH ,
GIVE ME A DISK .
UH , I NEED FRESH TELEPORTATION ,
S. BRUNDLE .
( Seth ) RUN SEQUENCE .
^ ^ ^
( telephone ringing )
HELLO ?
( heavy breathing on phone )
SETH .
SETH , I 'VE BEEN TRYING TO REACH YOU ,
WHERE ARE YOU ?
( Seth ) FOR THE LAST FOUR WEEKS , I 'VE BEEN AFRAID TO SEE YOU .
NOW , I 'M ... AFRAID NOT TO .
WHERE ARE YOU ?
ARE YOU AT HOME ?
( Seth ) VERONICA , YOU DON 'T KNOW , HOW RIGHT YOU WERE .
I 'VE GOTTEN MUCH , MUCH WORSE .
PLEASE , COME SEE ME- - PLEASE , COME NOW .
^ ^ ^
SETH , I 'M HERE .
( Seth ) STOP !
SETH !
YOU WERE RIGHT ,
I 'M DISEASED AND , UM ,
IT MIGHT BE CONTAGIOUS , SOMEHOW .
I WOULDN 'T WANT TO INFECT YOU .
AND IT 'S BEEN ACCELERATING .
IT 'S UNRELENTING- - EVERYDAY , THERE ARE CHANGES .
EVERY TIME I LOOK IN THE MIRROR ,
IT 'S SOMEONE DIFFERENT .
SOMEONE HIDEOUS- - REPULSIVE .
WHAT HAPPENED ?
^ I KNOW AN OLD LADY WHO SWALLOWED A FLY ^
^ PERHAPS , SHE 'LL DIE ^
SETH , PLEASE .
I WAS NOT PURE .
THE TELE-PORTER SYSTEM NEEDED PURE
AND I WAS NOT PURE .
I DON 'T KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN .
A FLY ...
GOT INTO THE TRANSMITTER POD WITH ME THAT FIRST TIME ,
WHEN I WAS ALONE .
UH , THE COMPUTER GOT CONFUSED .
THERE WEREN 'T SUPPOSED TO BE TWO SEPARATE GENETIC PATTERNS
AND IT DECIDED TO , UH , PLACE US TOGETHER .
IT MATED US , ME AND THE FLY .
WE HADN 'T EVEN BEEN PROPERLY INTRODUCED .
MY TELE-PORTER TURNED INTO A GENE SPLICER .
A VERY GOOD ONE , THOUGH .
I 'M NOT SETH BRUNDLE , ANYMORE .
I 'M THE OFFSPRING OF A BRUNDLE HOUSE FLY .
OH , GOD !
OH , GOD , SETH !
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY .
WHAT 'LL HAPPEN ?
WELL , I THINK IT 'S SHOWING ITSELF ,
AS A BIZARRE FORM OF CANCER .
A GENERAL CELLULAR CASE OF REVOLUTION GONE WRONG .
I 'M JUST GONNA DISINTEGRATE , IN A NOVEL WAY ...
AND THEN , I 'LL DIE AND THEN , IT WILL BE OVER .
NO-NO-NO- - I DON 'T ACCEPT THAT .
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING WE CAN DO .
YOU KNOW , SOMEBODY WE CAN GO TO ,
TESTS THAT CAN BE DONE .
( shouting ) NO !
UM , I WON 'T BE JUST ANOTHER TUMOROUS BORE ,
TALKING ENDLESSLY ABOUT HIS HAIR FALLING OUT
AND HIS LAST LYMPH NODES .
WELL , THEN , WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO ?
WHY DID YOU CALL ME ?
OH !
OH ...
THAT 'S DISGUSTING .
( gasping )
MY ... EAR- - NO !
I 'M SCARED .
HELP ME .
PLEASE , PLEASE , HELP ME .
DON 'T GO BACK TO HIM .
THAT 'S IT ?
THAT 'S YOUR ADVICE ?
HE 'S RIGHT- - DON 'T YOU SEE ,
IT COULD BE CONTAGIOUS .
IT COULD TURN INTO AN EPIDEMIC .
I HAVE TO GO BACK TO HIM .
I DON 'T BELIEVE THIS .
IF YOU SAW HIM , STATHIS ,
IF YOU SAW HOW SCARED AND ANGRY AND DESPERATE HE IS- -
I 'M SURE TYPHOID MARY WAS A VERY NICE PERSON , TOO ,
WHEN YOU SAW HER , SOCIALLY .
LISTEN , I DO NOT WANT YOU GOING- - I DON 'T CARE WHAT YOU WANT !
ALL RIGHT , FINE- - OKAY .
DO I HAVE PERMISSION TO CLAIM YOUR BODY ,
WHEN THIS IS ALL OVER ?
OH , GOD !
LOOK , HOW ABOUT THIS ...
YOU SAY , " IF ONLY I SAW HIM . "
SHOW ME .
TAPE HIM- - SHOW ME .
LET ME THINK ABOUT IT .
I 'LL COME UP WITH SOMETHING .
^ ^ ^
SETH ?
( Seth ) OH , UP HERE .
( surprised gasp )
GOTTEN PRETTY GOOD AT IT , HAVEN 'T I ?
YEAH , IT 'S ALMOST SECOND NATURE .
STOPPED BITING MY NAILS .
OH , LOOK AT THIS- - WHAT 'S THIS ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
I SEEM TO BE STRICKEN BY A DISEASE WITH A PURPOSE ,
WOULDN 'T YOU SAY ?
MAYBE , NOT SUCH A BAD DISEASE , AFTER ALL .
I CAN 'T STAY HERE .
NO-NO-NO .
WHY NOT- - WHY CAN 'T YOU ?
I CAN 'T TAKE IT- - IT 'S TOO MUCH .
WHAT 'S THERE TO TAKE ?
THE DISEASE HAS JUST REVEALED IT 'S PURPOSE .
WE DON 'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT CONTAGION , ANYMORE .
WHAT DOES THE DISEASE WANT ?
IT WANTS TO TURN ME INTO SOMETHING ELSE .
THAT 'S NOT TOO TERRIBLE IS IT ?
MOST PEOPLE WOULD GIVE ANYTHING
TO BE TURNED INTO SOMETHING ELSE .
TURNED INTO WHAT ?
WHAT DO YOU THINK , A FLY ?
I 'M BECOMING A 185 POUND FLY ?
NO , IT 'S SOMETHING THAT 'S NEVER EXISTED BEFORE .
I 'M BECOMING BRUNDLE FLY .
DON 'T YOU THINK THAT 'S WORTH A NOBEL PRIZE OR TWO ?
HERE , I 'LL MAKE YOU A DEMONSTRATION ,
THAT I THINK YOU 'LL WANT TO , UH , RECORD FOR POSTERITY .
I THINK IT MUST CHRONICLE
THE LIFE AND TIMES OF BRUNDLE FLY .
DON 'T YOU ?
AT THE VERY LEAST ,
IT SHOULD MAKE A FABULOUS CHILDREN 'S BOOK .
YOU SEEM TIRED .
YOU GOT ME THERE ?
HOW DOES BRUNDLE FLY EAT ?
WELL , HE FOUND OUT THE HARD AND PAINFUL WAY ,
THAT HE EATS VERY MUCH THE WAY A FLY EATS .
HIS TEETH ARE NOW USELESS ,
BECAUSE , ALTHOUGH HE CAN CHEW UP SOLID FOOD ,
HE CAN 'T DIGEST IT .
SOLID FOOD HURTS , SO , LIKE A FLY ,
BRUNDLE FLY BREAKS DOWN SOLIDS
WITH A CORROSIVE ENZYME ,
PLAYFULLY CALLED , VOMIT DROP .
HE REGURGITATES ON HIS FOOD , IT LIQUEFIES ,
AND THEN HE SUCKS IT BACK UP .
READY FOR A DEMONSTRATION KIDS ?
HERE GOES .
( vomiting )
OH , MY GOD !
MY , GOD !
( door opens )
HEY , RONNIE ?
RONNIE !
( crying )
WHAT IS IT ?
I 'M PREGNANT .
OH , NO !
I 'M PREGNANT WITH SETH 'S BABY .
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
I JUST ...
I WANT A DISK .
GIVE ME PRELIMINARY INTEGRATION .
( recording ) I WANT A DISK
( keeps repeating )
YOU 'RE A RELIC .
YES , YOU ARE- - YOU CAN 'T DENY IT .
PRESTIGIAL , ARCHEALOGICAL , REDUNDANT .
YOU 'VE MISSED SOME GOOD MOMENTS .
IS THAT WHY YOU 'RE HERE , TO CATCH UP ?
I WANTED ...
MY TEETH HAVE BEGUN TO FALL OUT .
THE MEDICINE CABINET 'S NOW
THE BRUNDLE MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY .
WANT TO SEE WHAT ELSE IS IN IT ?
NO .
THEN ... WHAT DO YOU WANT ?
I CAME TO TELL YOU , UM ...
I-I , JUST ...
I WANTED TO SEE YOU , BEFORE ...
^ ^ ^
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE , NOW ...
AND NEVER COME BACK HERE .
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF INSECT POLITICS ?
NEITHER HAVE I.
INSECTS DON 'T HAVE POLITICS .
THEY 'RE VERY BRUTAL .
NO COMPASSION , NO COMPROMISE .
WE CAN 'T TRUST THE INSECT .
I 'D LIKE TO BECOME THE FIRST INSECT POLITICIAN .
YOU SEE , I 'D LIKE TO , UM , BUT , UH , I 'M AFRAID OF ...
( crying ) I DON 'T KNOW WHAT YOU 'RE TRYING TO SAY .
I 'M SAYING ...
I 'M SAYING , I 'M AN INSECT ,
WHO DREAMT HE WAS A MAN , AND LOVED IT ,
BUT NOW , THE DREAM 'S OVER AND THE INSECT IS AWAKE .
NO , SETH .
I 'M SAYING ...
I 'LL HURT YOU , IF YOU STAY .
^ ^ ^
( door slams shut )
NO !
^ ^ ^
( sobbing ) LET 'S GO .
LET 'S DO IT , NOW .
NOW , WAIT .
WAIT A MINUTE- - WHAT DID HE SAY ?
I COULDN 'T TELL HIM- - LET 'S GO , NOW .
NO !
NO , I THINK WE SHOULD WAIT FOR A FEW DAYS .
I DON 'T THINK YOU 'RE IN THE RIGHT STATE OF MIND- - NO , NOW !
I WANT IT OUT OF MY BODY , NOW !
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN HIM ,
THERE COULD BE ANYTHING IN HERE ,
IN ME , IN MY BODY !
I DON 'T KNOW , IF I CAN ARRANGE IT , NOW ,
RIGHT NOW , TONIGHT .
WHY DO WE HAVE TO RUN AROUND IN THE DARK ,
LIKE A COUPLE OF- - CAUSE I DON 'T WANT IT IN MY BODY !
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME ?
I DON 'T WANT IT IN MY BODY !
( sobbing )
^ ^ ^
WELL , OKAY- - WHAT 'S THE STORY ?
SHE 'S PREGNANT ,
AND SHE WANTS TO HAVE AN ABORTION .
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT ?
WE HAVE GOOD REASON TO THINK ,
THAT THIS CHILD WILL BE DEFORMED .
YEAH , BUT , IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT ?
LOOK , FRANK ...
PLEASE .
IS IT YOUR CHILD ?
NO .
IT 'S THE ...
IT 'S THE CHILD OF A MAN WHO IS DEFORMED .
LISTEN , I DON 'T MEAN TO INTERFERE ,
BUT , I DETECT A CERTAIN , UNCERTAINTY HERE .
YOU KNOW , THERE ARE TESTS WE CAN DO
TO DETERMINE WHETHER OR NOT- - I DON 'T WANT TESTS .
TESTS CAN 'T GRANTEE ANYTHING .
THE BABY COULD START OFF NORMAL AND THEN , BECOME ...
I WANT AN ABORTION .
I 'LL DO IT MYSELF , IF I HAVE TO .
OKAY , IF YOU 'LL JUST SLIP INTO THAT ,
WE 'LL BE ON OUR WAY IN NO TIME .
^ ^ ^
( glass shattering ) ( screaming )
NO , NO !
WAIT , SETH- - NO !
^ ^ ^
WHY DID YOU WANT TO KILL THE BRUNDLE ?
THE BA ?
IT MIGHT BE ALL THAT 'S LEFT OF THE REAL ME .
PLEASE , DON 'T KILL ME .
I CAN 'T HAVE IT- - I 'M AFRAID .
PLEASE ...
HAVE THE BABY .
I CAN 'T- - I CAN 'T .
TOO BAD .
^ ^ ^
JESUS .
AH !
( painful screaming )
^ ^ ^
( screaming )
NO , DON 'T-DON 'T- - PLEASE , PLEASE .
^ ^ ^
HELP ME .
HELP ME TO BE HUMAN .
HOW ?
WELL ...
I GO THERE ...
AND , UH , YOU GO THERE .
AHHH !
WE ... GO APART ,
THEN-THEN WE COME TOGETHER THERE .
YOU , ME AND THE BABY , TOGETHER .
^ ^ ^
NO .
WE 'LL BE THE ULTIMATE FAMILY .
A FAMILY OF THREE , JOINED TOGETHER IN ONE BODY .
MORE HUMAN , THAN I AM ALONE .
NO .
NO-NO !
( screaming )
NO !
^ ^ ^
OH , GOD , PLEASE !
NO !
( screaming )
NO-NO !
^ ^ ^
OH , GOD !
( glass breaking )
^ ^ ^
( Veronica panting )
( ominous scream )
( sobbing )
^ ^ ^
NO !
I CAN 'T !
( sobbing hysterically )
^ ^ ^